

IT Project Manager taraj@isp.com 0114 222 1122

London, United Kingdom

Tara Jones

Profile

Energetic IT Project Manager with a proven reputation for leading exceptional IT project design, execution, and completion. High-impact team leader, known for motivating expert groups to deliver on ambitious project objectives. Demonstrated capacity for shaping innovative technology solutions in alignment with unique corporate goals.

Employment History

Technical Programme Manager at LinkedIn, London, UK

02/2019-Present

- Direct a 12-person team in the creation and delivery of customer-facing tools, monitoring progress for alignment with project parameters, LinkedIn brand standards, and user needs.
- Rationalised a wide range of proposed projects into a single cohesive oragnisational roadmap, prioritising initiatives based on urgency, brand priorities, and impact.
- Successfully executed up to 10 new tool, functionality, or experience releases per quarter.

Technical Project Manager at Pearson, London, UK

01/2016-01/2019

- Shaped and defined project methodology, embedding agile approaches and scrum frameworks to maximise team-wide efficiency.
- Oversaw project framework, monitoring progress through daily scrum meetings and planning sessions to drive completion of key phases.
- Partnered with leadership to identify key project and business goals, establishing long-term, two-year project roadmaps.

Education

Master of Science in Information Technology, University of East London, London, UK

08/2012-11/2015

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology, University of East London, London, UK

08/2008-05/2012

Skills

Project Management	5/5
IT Programme Management	5/5
Team Leadership	5/5
Agile Methodologies	4/5
Scrum Frameworks	4/5
IT Engineering	5/5

Languages

French	Highly	proficient
Spanish	Very good	command